我记得我步出火焰,
黑暗中一个模糊的身影,
I remember stepping from the fIames,
a vague shape in the dark,
之后又没了.
then nothing.
直到2天后
我发现自己又重新站在了
UntiI I found myseIf standing
by the coId remains of our campfire
已经熄灭的篝火旁.
two days Iater.
少校, 有一些
新科技
Major, there are
some new techniques
或许能帮我们突破
您的失忆症.
that might help us break through
your amnesia.
我的记忆对逆行复原
已经免疫了.
My memories are immune
from regression.
我能感觉到它们, 几乎触手可及,
那气息和情绪.
I can feeI them, they are paIpabIe,
the smeIIs and sensation.
然而,近在眼前,
却又远在天边.
Everything is known to me,
yet somehow beyond my reach.
你还记得其它的事吗?
Do you remember anything else?
几乎没有.
Very IittIe.
除了一个影像挥之不去
一只巨大的猫头鹰.
Save for one disturbing image
of a giant owI.
- 四处瀰漫着.
- 一只巨大的猫头鹰?
- Pervasive.
- A giant owl?
一只巨大的猫头鹰? 多大
A giant owI? How big?
大的足以包着我的头
还有我的记忆.
Enough to cIoud my mind
and memory.
有3个比例完美的三角形疤痕
在右耳后.
Three trianguIar scars behind
the right ear in perfect proportion.
布里格斯少校,
Major Briggs,
严格来说,你的工作
到底涉及到哪方面?
exactIy what does
your work invoIve?
关于哪方面,
That information's,
正如我对自己
永无休止的重复一样,
as I've repeated endIessIy
to myseIf,
只能说是指定机密.
cIassified.
虽然对我来说,守着这些秘密
已经没什么重大意义了.
Though the keeping of secrets
seems Iess meaningfuI to me now.
可能某些信息的源头
是如此重要
Perhaps there are sources
of information that are so important
以至于超越了人类
所能理解的范畴.
as to transcend the human need
to conspire.
当信息赋予了重量时,
就不再从属于--
Information of such weight,
that pertains not--
噢, 天啊.
Oh, God.
这是意味着灵魂?
Is this meant for the souI?
我的灵魂?
My souI?
少校, 也许你最好
还是从头开始讲吧.
Major, perhaps you'd better
start back at the beginning.
你熟知
蓝空计划书吗?
Are you famiIiar
with Project BIue Book?
是的, 先生, 我知道.
Yes, sir, I am.
空军对不明飞行物等
超自然现象
The Air Force investigation
into the phenomena
的调查计划.
of unidentified fIying objects.
1969正式解散了.
OfficiaIIy disbanded in 1 969.
但我们当中还有人
But there are those of us
以非官方的身份,
在继续进行着这项目,
who continue,
in an unofficiaI capacity,
和之前一样监测着天空.
examining the heavens as before.
就像在双峰镇这里,
我们正在的地底下.
In the case of Twin Peaks,
the earth beIow.
寻找着一个叫
守日门的地方.
We are searching for a pIace
caIIed the White Lodge.
- 布里格斯少校?
- 我一直在等你们呢.
- Major Briggs?
- I've been expecting you.
- 等会儿, 伙计们.
- 莱利上校的命令.
- HoId on just a minute, feIIows.
- CoIoneI RiIey's orders.
我才不管谁的命令,
I don't care what orders you've got,
这是我的地盘,而布里格斯少校
正巧是一个朋友的--
this is my station and Major Briggs
happens to be a friend of--
哈里.
Harry.
恐怕我们要迟些日子
才能继续讨论这个话题了.
I'm afraid we wiII have to continue
this discussion at a Iater date.
你肯定
自己想跟他们走吗?
Are you sure
you wanna go with them?
是的.
Yeah.
- 再见.
- 少校.
- Goodbye.
- Major.
哦, 自在点儿, 尔尼, 它又不咬人的.
Oh, go ahead, Ernie, it won't bite.
你知道什么, 哥们儿.
A Iot you know, paI.
这些人都是些危险的恶棍,
These men are dangerous thugs,
可和我以前见过的暴类们比
他们还嫌嫩呢.
not that I haven't met
pIenty of their kind before.
没错,尚·雷诺是个硬汉,
Jean RenauIt is a hard man,
但我知道还有人
能让他浑身发抖呢.
but I've known men
that wouId make him quiver.
尔尼, 少来了.
Ernie, come on.
打电话吧.
Make the caII.
那, 买卖都设计好了?
WeII, have we set the buy yet?
正努力呢.
尔尼还是有点点怕怕呢.
Trying to.
Ernie's a wee bit gun-shy.
怕怕?
Gun-shy?
尔尼·奈尔斯可是胆大包天的角儿.
看我搞定他.
Ernie NiIes is as boId as can be.
Let me at him.
求你了,还是别让我干这个了.
PIease don't make me do this.
这简直就是自杀, 我知道的.
拜托了, 就当我求你了, 别.
This is suicide, I know.
PIease, I'm begging you, pIease.
算大家行行好, 别.
For everybody's sake, pIease.
尔尼, 尔尼, 尔尼.
Ernie, Ernie, Ernie.
喂.
HeIIo.
麻烦你,
我找尚·雷诺?
May I speak to Jean RenauIt,
pIease?
嗨, 尚. 是啊, 我已经把一个外地
的大买家带来了.
Hi, Jean. Yeah, I've got
that big out-of-town buy here.
嗨, 露西.
Hi, Lucy.
你去哪儿了, 安德鲁?
Where have you been, Andrew?
刚有一辆车撞到树了.
There was a cat in a tree.
做一个警员
就是永不得安宁.
A peace officer's work
is never done.
但我们走运了, 我去搞的部分
已经有大收获了.
But fortunateIy for us, my efforts
have borne more paIatabIe fruit.
我去了一趟快乐帮手
的收养中介所,
I paid the Happy HeIping Hand
adoption agency a visit,
那里的几个蓝发女子
都非常买我帐
where severaI bIue-haired Iadies
were onIy too happy to sup
高兴的不得了.
from my open paIm.
不幸的是,
小尼克的档案已经被封存了
UnfortunateIy,
IittIe Nicky's records have been seaIed
送回孤儿院去了.
and returned to the orphanage.
那我们永远都不可能知道
小尼克的父母出过什么事了.
We'II never know what reaIIy happened
to IittIe Nicky's parents.
别泄气, 安德鲁.
别绝望, 亲爱的同志.
Courage, Andrew.
Do not despair, dear boy.
下一站,
孤儿院也不过如是.
Next stop,
that seIfsame orphanage.
小尼克的档案在里面呢.
And IittIe Nicky's records within.
- 或许我们该告诉露西.
-  绝对不行.
- Maybe we shouId teII Lucy.
- AbsoIuteIy not.
这样, 亲爱的同志,
这完全是男人间的事.
This, dear boy,
is strictIy a man's job.
跟我来.
FoIIow me.
- 露西.
- 嗨.
- Lucy.
- Hi.
有什么好消息?
Any Iuck?
名单上每份国家报的个人信息栏
我都查过了,
I checked the personaIs coIumns
in every nationaI newspaper on the Iist,
没有一个看来像
棋局的启示
and I didn't see anything
that Iooked Iike a chess deaI
也没发现叫
云顿·厄尔的.
or find any mention
of the name Windom EarIe.
不好意思.
I'm sorry.
没关系.
It's okay.
再来点咖啡?
More coffee?
没错.
You bet.
一切都还好吧, 艾德?
Is everything aII right, Ed?
好的不能再好了.
CouIdn't be better.
这是给你的.
This is for you.
那先就这样吧.
Bye for now.
再见.
Bye-bye.
来吧, 里欧.
Come on, Leo.
那才是乖里欧.
That's a good Leo.
每天带来新开始.
Each day brings a new beginning.
每一小时, ...的承诺
And every hour, the promise of...
本来是轮到你喂他的, 波比!
It was your turn to feed him, Bobby!
我要练习.
I got practice.
足球季早结束了.
FootbaII season is over.
是棒球.
我们的全国民娱活动呢
BasebaII.
Our nationaI pastime?
那好. 那你回来后
就能清理了吧.
Fine. You can cIean
when you get back.
我不回来了.
I ain't coming back.
什么?
What?
你眼前正站着
本·荷恩的新宠儿呢.
You're Iooking
at Ben Horne's brand-new boy.
"黄金机会"这个词
对你没有任何意义吗?
Do the words ''goIden opportunity''
mean anything to you?
这次我可是鸿运当头了, 雪莉.
This is my big break, SheIIy.
你不觉得
比起给·强生洗泡泡浴
You don't think
I have anything better to do
我应该去做
更好的事吗?
than give Leo Johnson
a bubbIe bath?
那我怎么办, 波比?
And what about me, Bobby?
难道我就没有更好事去做了吗?
Do I not have anything better to do?
我所能想到的，没有.
Not that I can think of.
波比.
Bobby.
波比!
Bobby!
上帝!
God!
大个儿艾德加油站.
Big Ed's Gas Farm.
- 艾德叔叔?
-  詹姆斯?
- UncIe Ed?
- James?
- 是啊, 是我.
- 你在哪啊? 你一切都好吧?
- Yeah, it's me.
- Where are you? Are you all right?
哦, 我很好.
Oh, I'm okay.
看, 帮我个忙.
Look, I need a favor.
我需要你帮我把我银行帐户里
存款全都拿出来.
I need you to get aII the money
out of my savings account.
可那里只有12美元, 詹姆斯.
That's only $ 1 2, James.
也好, 不管多少都好吧.
WeII, whatever's Ieft.
然后汇到沃里，一个96号公路边上的酒吧
写我收就行了.
And send it care of me to WaIIies.
It's this bar out on 96.
你遇到麻烦了吗?
Are you in trouble?
不是, 我现在不方便说.
No, I reaIIy can't taIk about it.
- 詹姆斯--
- 听着, 我要挂机了.
- James--
- Listen, I reaIIy can't taIk right now.
- 那好.
- 我们见面再说吧.
- Okay.
- We'II taIk about it soon.
- 保重.
- 好的.
- Take care.
- Yeah.
- 再电联.
- 好的, 再见.
- Call soon.
- Okay, bye.
- 长途?
- 打回双峰镇的.
- Long-distance?
- Twin Peaks.
你想家了, 詹姆斯?
Are you homesick, James?
不.
No.
跟我聊聊双峰镇吧.
TeII me about Twin Peaks.
那没什么好说.
There's nothing to say.
那你可以说说为什么离开那儿.
You couId start with why you Ieft.
我记得, 是关于一个女人.
It was a woman, as I recaII.
不, 你说过是几个.
No, you said it was a few of them.
一个我心爱的女孩死了.
I Ioved a girI who died.
她叫劳拉.
Her name was Laura.
我以为我了解她,
但其实不是.
And I thought I knew her,
but I didn't.
我猜谁都不了解她.
I guess nobody did.
为你感到难过.
I'm sorry.
你知道吗?
之前,我一直以为自己活的很有意义
My Iife used to make sense,
you know?
虽然我也并不是整天都觉得有意义,
但毕竟是我自己的生活.
I didn't Iike it aII the time,
but it was mine.
至少我感觉它属于我的.
And I feIt Iike it beIonged to me.
然而劳拉死了.
And then Laura died.
现在我发现,我反过来从属于生活了.
And now I beIong to something eIse.
从属于劳拉.
To Laura.
无论我做什么,
And no matter what I did,
又或是我尽多少努力想去改变...
or how much I tried to heIp...
...却无法阻止另一个女孩被杀.
...another girI got murdered.
最后,我只想骑上我的机车
远走高飞.
I just wanted to get on my bike
and ride away.
一走了之, 甩开双峰镇的那些事
能甩多远就甩多远.
Take off, just go as far from
Twin Peaks as the thing wiII take me.
我知道那种感觉, 詹姆斯.
I know the feeIing, James.
我知道那种感觉.
I know the feeIing.
你为什么任由他伤害你?
Why do you Iet him hurt you?
杰弗里要走了.
Jeffrey's Ieaving.
我需要你. 你会帮助我吗?
I need you. WiII you heIp me?
- 玛舒先生.
- 你什么意思?
- Mr. Marsh.
- What do you mean?
- 我需要你的帮助.
- 我会帮你把袋子放进去的.
- I need your heIp.
- I'II put the bags in for you.
很好, 先生.
Very good, sir.
- 早安, 迈克·尼森.
- 噢, 不是吧.
- Good morning, Mike NeIson.
- Oh, Lord.
你要和我共饮一杯汽水吗?
You wanna share a soda?
要不来一大块樱桃馅饼
也可以? 2个叉子.
How about a nice big piece
of cherry pie? Two forks.
赫尔利, 纳丁,
我只想点自己的樱桃馅饼.
Mrs. HurIey, Nadine,
I want my own piece of cherry pie.
事实上, 我想要2块
樱桃馅饼, 我自己吃.
In fact, I want two pieces
of cherry pie, by myseIf.
那好. 点肉卷.
Okay. Meat Ioaf.
不要. 只要樱桃馅饼和咖啡.
其实, 我要16杯咖啡.
No. Cherry pie and coffee.
In fact, I want 1 6 cups of coffee.
我不想和你聊,
也不想和你走.
I don't wanna taIk with you,
waIk with you.
更不想见到你,
甚至不想认识你.
I don't wanna see you,
I don't wanna know you.
我说的够清楚了吧,懂了吗?
Is that cIear enough to understand?
还是需要我去法院申请禁制令
才能彻底让你明白呢?
Or do I need a court order
to get my point across?
迈克·尼森,
Mike NeIson,
你是我见过的最最
帅气的男生.
you are the handsomest boy
I've ever known.
我真的会非常高兴
And I wouId reaIIy Iike it
如果你能和我约会一次.
if you and I couId go out on a date.
对不起了.
I'm sorry.
有时我就是忍不住.
Sometimes I can't heIp myseIf.
嘿, 诺玛. 准备上哪儿去?
Hey, Norma. Where are you going?
去办点事.
I have to run some errands.
现在出去办事, 太早了点吧?
It's a IittIe earIy for errands, isn't it?
早市还没过呢
这么多人在.
We've stiII got most
of the breakfast crowd.
只要有你和厨房里有充足的炒蛋
就够了.
Just you and a kitchen fuII
of scrambIed eggs.
我去去就回.
I'II be right back.
就当是个员工测试好了, 汉克.
Just think of it as a test, Hank.
我会的.
I'II do that.
我还以为你会搬进
我那里去住.
I thought you were moving
into my pIace.
- 对不起.
- 到底怎么了?
- I'm sorry.
- What happened?
你留在这儿鬼地方干嘛呀?
What the heII are you doing here?
- 这是我的家.
- 家?
- This is my home.
- Home?
在凯萨琳对你做过那些事后
你还当这儿是家?
After everything Catherine
has done to you?
我别无选择.
I have no choice.
乔西.
Josie.
- 噢, 回家吧.
- 乔西, 让我来照顾你吧.
- Oh, go home.
- Josie, Iet me take care of you.
- 不.
- 求你了.
- No.
- PIease.
听着, 我在这里安全.
而我留在这儿,
Listen, I'm safe here.
And when I'm here,
- 你也安全.
- 不.
- you're safe too.
- No.
停下.
Stop.
看看我.
Look at me.
我现在是凯萨琳的女佣.
I'm Catherine's maid.
我配不起你了.
I'm no good for you.
你配的起.
You are good for me.
我爱你.
I Iove you.
我要你.
I want you.
露西尔...
LuciIIe...
怎么了?
What?
出什么事了?
What's wrong?
是, 先生, 将军.
Yes, sir, generaI.
我要你在小圆坡那里
负责带领人马.
I want you to Iead the charge
on LittIe Round Top.
是的, 先生.
Yes, sir.
是的, 先生!
Yes, sir!
斯丢尔将军在哪儿?
还有他的骑兵团呢?
And where is GeneraI Stuart?
And his cavaIry?
他马上到, 先生.
他那该死的眼睛.
He's a-coming, sir.
Damn his eyes.
- 他来了, 先生. 我就知道!
- 爸爸!
- He's coming, sir. I know it!
- Daddy!
- 他要来了. 那他最好快来送死.
- 爸爸.
- He's coming. He had better be.
- Daddy.
为了我们大家而战.
For aII our sakes.
因为敌人,
我们在这与敌人相遇.
Because the enemy,
we meet the enemy here.
在早晨之前见他.
We meet him before morning.
- 我们在这见他.
- 爸爸.
- We meet him here.
- Daddy.
怎么, 亲爱的?
Yes, darIing?
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
一场大战爆发了, 亲爱的.
There's a war going on, darIing.
一场战争?
A war?
州际大战.
A war between the states.
爸爸, 我觉得你需要帮助.
Daddy, I think you need some heIp.
不, 不, 我很好, 亲爱的.
No, no, I'm aII right, darIing.
我需要的只是一点时间.
这是一个非常重要的日子.
I just need a IittIe time.
This is a very important day.
是的, 爸爸,
的确是一个非常重要的日子.
Yes, Daddy,
this is a very important day.
我们要挽救家里的生意.
We're gonna save the business.
- 你和我.
- 亲爱的, 亲爱的.
- You and I.
- DarIing, darIing.
怎么呢, 爸爸?
Yes, Daddy?
你正踩着斯丢尔将军呢.
You are standing on GeneraI Stuart.
李将军!
GeneraI Lee!
李将军! 是, 先生.
老桀, 他已经来了.
GeneraI Lee! Yes, sir.
OId Jeb, he's come.
噢, 我不再要那些战车了!
Oh, I don't need any more wagons!
我要我的耳目
在身边.
I want my eyes
and my ears beside me.
- 把斯丢尔将军给我找来.
- 我是欧蕊.
- Get me GeneraI Stuart.
- This is Audrey.
- 请帮我接杰里·荷恩.
- 把诺顿将军给我带来.
- I need you to get me Jerry Horne.
- Bring me GeneraI Norton.
- 15号在亚拉巴马州准备好人马.
- 有急事.
- Ready the men of the AIabama 1 5th.
- This is an emergency.
- 我一直在想我们得--
- 我想我们需要谈谈那个--
- I've been figuring that we have to--
- I think we need to taIk about what--
进来吧.
Come on in.
你先说.
You first.
好.
Okay.
我夜思的
是你.
You're the Iast thing I think of
when I go to sIeep at night.
每天早晨起来
我日想的
And you're the first thought
on my mind
还是你.
when I get up in the morning.
我知道这个世界正走向毁灭,
I know this worId is going to pieces,
而它好像故意
要把我们分开.
and it feeIs Iike it's designed
to keep us apart.
但我们仍深爱对方, 艾德.
But we Iove each other, Ed.
我要和你在一起.
I wanna be with you.
无论发生什么事
我只想和你在一起.
I wanna be with you
no matter what happens.
艾德, 艾德, 艾德. 该你说了.
Ed, Ed, Ed. Your turn.
等一下再说吧.
Later.
你看着点儿胸毛,
行吗?
WiII you mind the chest hair,
wiII you?
你就像只大汗猪, 尼尔先生.
You're sweating Iike a pig, Mr. NiIes.
哦,是吗， 那多谢了.
Oh, thanks a Iot.
那是神经紧张性出汗, 伙计.
就是多汗症.
That's nervous perspiration, man.
Hyperhidrosis.
一个儿时的病了.
It's a chiIdhood condition.
我一直没留意自己有这个病，直到
打朝鲜战争, 还记得那些年吗?
I didn't notice it tiII the war.
Korea, remember that year?
我当时正领着一个营
向49号地平线进发.
I was Ieading a battaIion
up towards the 49th paraIIeI.
大家都不过是一帮
小毛孩罢了.
We were just a bunch
of fresh-faced kids.
我不知道当时
走进了一个什么鬼地方.
I didn't know what kind of heII
we were stepping into.
尔尼. 尔尼, 我要你集中精神
在这里的这一刻.
Ernie. Ernie, I want you to focus
on the here and now.
你把指令一个一个向我
重复一遍.
Repeat your instructions to me
step by step.
好的.
Okay.
我带迪尼斯去死狗庄.
I take Denise up to Dead Dog Farm.
- 我介绍她给雷诺.
- 对.
- I introduce her to RenauIt.
- Right.
全程引导雷诺买卖,
I take RenauIt through the buy,
完成交易后
就离开那里.
compIete the transaction
and get the heII out of there.
好. 哈里?
那时你就冲进去.
Good. Harry?
That's when you come in.
哎呀, 我真希望
能参与到其中啊.
By goIIy, I sure wish
I couId join you feIIas.
但目前，我暂时失去了
我的执法权.
But I've temporariIy Iost
my enforcement franchise.
- 就是.
- 那好,
- I'II bet.
- WeII,
那事儿，
我一直在琢磨着.
I've been giving that
some thought.
你就在这做代理警员好了.
Consider yourseIf deputized.
不打东家，打西家.
The Bureau's Ioss is my gain.
希望我不会辜负这警章.
I hope I can Iive up to this.
都装好了. 我们出发前
你们或许想把他擦干咯.
He's done. You might wanna
toweI him off before we go.
少来了.
Come on.
我完成买卖后
How Iong wiII it take you guys
你们要多久
才会攻进来?
to storm the farmhouse
after I compIete the buy?
你一出来, 我们就进去.
You go out, we come in.
- 我能问你个问题吗?
- 什么, 尔尼?
- Can I ask you a question?
- What, Ernie?
别逼我干这个了.
这可不是我的行当.
Don't make me do this.
This isn't my Iine of work.
我承认我是个懦夫. 没胆干
这事儿, 我只是个会计师.
I'm a coward. I don't do
this kind of thing, I'm a CPA.
- 尔尼.
- Ernie.
只是一时失控.
看, 我冷静了.
Just a momentary Iapse.
Look, I'm cooI.
我们出发吧, 哼?
Let's go do it, huh?
- 迪尼斯在哪儿?
- 我还没见到她.
- Where's Denise?
- I haven't seen her.
你可以叫我丹尼斯了.
You can caII me Dennis.
噢, 我搞不懂,
不知怎的，这身打扮看来更合适.
Oh, I don't know,
somehow it seemed more appropriate.
你们觉得呢?
What do you think?
我们的调查
必须秘密进行.
Our investigation
must proceed sub rosa.
我们可能还得撬门而入.
见机行事.
We may have to pick the Iock.
Tricky business.
可不是.　我们进来了.
VoiIa. We enter.
- 其他人呢?
- 午餐去了.
- Where is everybody?
- Lunch.
在这儿呢, 案子的卷宗.
Here we are, the case fiIes.
尼, 尼.
N, N.
尼, 尼 !
N, N !
尼奥斯, 尼斯特,
尼德比, 尼得门.
NaiIs, Neaster,
Neatherby, NeedIeman.
尼古拉斯·尼得门,
我们的小尼克.
NichoIas NeedIeman,
our IittIe Nicky.
- 我们可以在车上看.
- 耐心点, 安德鲁.
- We can read it in the car.
- Patience, Andrew.
- 基巴.
- 日常背景资料.
- Dick.
- The usuaI background information.
出生地,
BirthpIace,
首次领养记录.
initiaI adoption.
几次中的头一次, 看来.
First of severaI, it seems.
基巴.
Dick.
事态越来越复杂了.
The pIot thickens.
秘密在哪儿呢, 小尼克?
Where are thy secrets, IittIe Nicky?
基巴.
Dick.
嗨.
Hi.
我们是绷斯顿夫妇.
We're the Brunstons.
我知道我们来的早了点.
I know we're a IittIe earIy.
只是我们太急于想
见到他了.
It's just that we're so darn eager
to see him.
我们能见他了吗? 唐尼在哪儿?
Can we see him? Where is Donnie?
小唐尼死了.
LittIe Donnie is dead.
我的意思是累死了.
Dead tired, I mean.
恐怕小唐尼他,
今天不是很舒服.
I'm afraid IittIe Donnie,
he isn't feeIing up to snuff.
呀, 他昨天还
好好的.
WeII, he was in perfect heaIth
onIy yesterday.
- 基巴.
- 稍等一会儿.
- Dick.
- Just a minute.
木头人, 就让我们帮这些好人
帮到底吧.
Woody, Iet me finish heIping
these good peopIe.
那么, 我们刚讲到哪儿了?
Now, where were we?
艾德. 艾德, 我是唐娜.
Ed. Ed, it's Donna.
- 我需要你的帮助, 艾德.
- 我能为你做点什么, 宝贝?
- I need your heIp, Ed.
- What can I do for you, honey?
嗯, 我一直在找詹姆斯.
WeII, I've been Iooking for James.
他一直没来学校,
在双食店也没见过他.
He hasn't been in schooI,
no one's seen him at the diner.
我还去过他家,
但还是找不着他.
I even went by his house,
but I can't find him.
听着, 詹姆斯很好. 他来过电话了.
Listen, James is fine. He caIIed.
他要我给他汇些钱去
在96号公路边的一个酒吧转给他.
He asked me to send him some money
in care of a bar out on 96.
我们没说太久.
We didn't taIk Iong.
- 我只知道这些.
- 让我来给他送钱吧.
- It's aII I know.
- I'II take it to him.
那好, 那你怎么跟家里说?
WeII, what about your foIks?
我会解释, 他们会理解的.
I'II expIain, they'II understand.
- 好吧.
- 谢谢, 艾德.
- Okay.
- Thanks, Ed.
我得走了.
I have to get going.
回头给你电话.
I'II caII.
- 我们还有好多话没讲.
- 就是.
- We have a Iot to taIk about.
- Yeah.
- 再见.
- Bye.
噢, 艾德. 这是我们为了所爱而做的.
Oh, Ed. The things we do for Iove.
小艾艾, 我回来啦.
Eddie, I'm home.
小艾艾! 小心!
Eddie! Look out!
好你个大孬种!
You big buIIy!
小艾艾?
Eddie?
你能听见我说话吗?
Can you hear me?
- 纳丁?
- 是的, 纳丁在这儿呢.
- Nadine?
- Yeah, Nadine's here.
你什么事都不用担心, 宝贝.
Don't you worry about a thing, baby.
让纳丁来处理就好了.
Nadine wiII take care of everything.
张伯伦上校
在20号缅因州的
CoIoneI ChamberIain
and the 20th Maine
小圆顶首脑会议
已经身陷囵圄了.
were trapped at the summit
of LittIe Round Top.
现在, 他唯一的机会
Now, his onIy chance
就是调遣他的军团到
is to maneuver his Ieft fIank
左翼山坡下
形成一道翼闸.
down the hiIIside
Iike a swinging gate.
但我们都为他设计好了, 波比.
But we were waiting for him, Bobby.
等张伯伦使完最后的
绝招, 波比, 他就完蛋了.
And ChamberIain's desperate
maneuver ended, Bobby, in faiIure.
- 荷恩先生--
- 到时小圆顶, 波比, 就是我们的了.
- Mr. Horne--
- LittIe Round Top, Bobby, was ours.
凭着这些制高点, 我们就能
击退联邦阵线.
From that vantage point, we were abIe
to roII back the FederaI Iines.
威武的皮克特
就能大展雄风了, 波比.
Setting the stage
for Pickett's mighty charge, Bobby.
还有胜利!
And victory!
胜利. 好哇，万岁.
Victory. Hurray.
米德将军,
GeneraI Meade,
你为失败而名誉扫地，饱受煎熬.
you have suffered an ignobIe defeat.
我接受
你无条件投降.
And I accept
your unconditionaI surrender.
那好, 就告诉你, 荷恩先生.
Okay, teII you what, Mr. Horne.
我打算先去和
林肯总统谈谈, 好吗?
I'm gonna go and taIk
to President LincoIn first, okay?
那么,你就在这乖乖的给我等着...
So you just wait right here and...
然后我再回来
和你继续投降事宜.
And I'II get back to you
on this whoIe surrender thing.
就这样咯? 得走了.
Okay? Gotta go.
让总统
久等了可不好.
Don't wanna keep
the president waiting.
先生!
Sir!
宝贝儿, 我有一个好消息
和一个坏消息.
Baby, I got some good news
and I got some bad news.
坏消息就是你老爸
刚在费城买了一个商品房.
The bad news is that your oId man
just bought a condo in FIip City.
好消息就是他就要
打赢内战了.
The good news is that he's about
to win the CiviI War.
我知道.
I know.
杰里叔叔说他
下一班机就到.
UncIe Jerry said he was coming home
on the next pIane.
杰柯比医生则说
他尽可能明天赶过来.
Dr. Jacoby said
he wouId come over tomorrow.
我觉得要给爸爸打一针了.
I think Daddy needs an injection.
上帝, 我们得想办法帮帮他.
God, we gotta heIp him.
别担心, 宝贝儿,
有波比在呢.
Don't worry, baby,
Bobby's on the case.
别叫我宝贝儿.
Don't caII me baby.
自己进来吧.
Enter IiveIy.
凯萨琳.
Catherine.
你好啊, 本.
HeIIo, Ben.
你是来幸灾乐祸的吧,
是吧?
You've come here to gIoat,
haven't you?
来看我怎么个死法.
To ceIebrate my demise.
好, 请便吧. 尽情嘲笑我吧.
WeII, you go ahead. You Iaugh.
你打败我了...
You defeated me...
...就像我打败了米德将军一样.
...as I have defeated GeneraI Meade.
是的.
It's true.
我是来幸灾乐祸的.
I did come here to gIoat.
你欺骗和出卖了我.
You doubIe-crossed me.
你还想杀死我.
You tried to kiII me.
我真想把你埋葬到深坑里
And I wanted to bury you so deepIy
深的可以让子孙后代还能
挖出你那肮脏的残骸,好让大家都看看清楚.
that future generations wouId unearth
and exhibit your remains.
你内里那一坨鼻涕一样蠕动的混帐大肠钩虫.
SIimy rat bastard Americanus.
不可依靠.
Do not feed.
不可信任.
Do not trust.
我想...
I suppose...
...我是不那么值得信赖.
...that I'm not that trustworthy.
不管怎样
我还是了解你的,
Despite everything
I know about you,
我发现自己这一刻和你一起在这里.
I find myseIf here with you.
就想要你.
Wanting you.
你不是说真的吧.
You can't be serious.
我要你, 本.
I want you, Ben.
我也感到很震撼,
但却无法逃避.
Horrifying as it seems,
I can't escape it.
你...
You...
你就是让我激动的浑身发颤.
You make my body hum.
吻我, 李将军.
Kiss me, GeneraI Lee.
向胜利前进!
On to victory!
走快点, 吉.
香槟都变暖了.
Hurry up, Jim.
The champagne's getting warm.
别叫我吉.
Don't caII me Jim.
到了, 到了, 到了.
AII right, aII right, aII right.
- 詹姆斯, 怎么了?
- 你可以看了!
- James, what?
- You may Iook!
想去兜兜风吗?
Any pIace you wanna go?
杰弗里午夜才回来.
Jeffrey wiII be home by midnight.
这样,我们不有很多时间了吗?
Doesn't Ieave us a Iot of time.
好, 看我们都能干点什么.
WeII, I'II take what we can get.
成交.
It's a deaI.
敬英俊的陌生人.
To handsome strangers.
和修好的引擎.
And rebuiIt engines.
你知道吗, 我以为它
再也开不动了.
You know, I never thought
I'd see it drive again.
你是一个神奇工匠.
You're a miracIe worker.
不, 真的.
No, honest.
你太谦虚了.
You're being too modest.
噢, 来嘛. 你配的.
Oh, go on. You deserve it.
你坚强又和善.
You're strong and you're kind.
你有一张极其真诚的脸,
詹姆斯.
You have a wonderfuIIy honest face,
James.
别笑, 这相当宝贵.
Don't Iaugh, it's quite rare.
每当我看着你,
我能准确的说出你的心在想什么.
Every time I Iook at you,
I couId teII exactIy what you're thinking.
那, 我最好还是小心点
别胡思乱想.
WeII, I'd better be carefuI
about what I'm thinking.
别为了我.
Don't be too carefuI.
变小心眼了.
Not on my account.
那么, 你接下来有什么计划?
So, what are your pIans?
我其实真没什么计划.
I don't reaIIy have any pIans.
你会去哪儿?
Where wiII you go?
我不知道.
I don't know.
- 詹姆斯, 别.
- 别什么?
- James, don't.
- What?
我不想你离开.
I don't want you to Ieave.
给我多些时间, 詹姆斯.
Give me some more time, James.
我能想出一百个理由
让你留下来.
I can think of a hundred reasons
for you to stay.
你肯定你不想等
汉克来吗?
You sure you don't wanna wait
for Hank?
他今早告诉我
他这次想全程参与的.
He toId me this morning
he wanted in on aII of this.
- 我觉得我们该等等--
- 没有他,我们也要开始的.
- I think we shouId wait--
- We'II start without him.
随你怎么说吧.
Whatever you say.
你在冒大汗.
有什么不妥吗?
You're sweating.
Is something wrong?
冒汗? 你不知道, 是多汗症.
儿时的病.
Sweaty. You know, it's hyperhidrosis.
It's a chiIdhood condition.
我在关岛住的时候
染过黄热病.
I was Iiving in Guam at the time
I contracted yeIIow fever.
这是恶性后遗症.
The effects are vicious.
你知道, 社交里不受欢迎的
其中之一就是冒汗.
You know, sweating is one
of the more sociaIIy unacceptabIe.
坐下, 尔尼. 放松点.
Sit down, Ernie. Take a deep breath.
- 为是不容.
- 看来都很妥当了.
- SociaIIy unacceptabIe.
- Everything seems to be in order.
我们能快点搞完吗?
我还得赶飞机.
Do you think we couId hurry this up?
I got a pIane to catch.
尚. 尚, 看看,
他的衬衫在冒烟.
Jean. Jean, take a Iook,
his shirt is smoking.
信号中断了.
The wire's dead.
库珀!
Cooper!
- 库珀!
- 库.
- Cooper!
- Coop.
他是冲我来的, 哈里.
He came for me, Harry.
我要安全过境.
I want safe passage to the border.
首先把人质放了.
First, reIease the hostages.
看来我们话不投机, 库珀.
We're at cross-purposes, Cooper.
如果你不,我们会杀了你.
We'II kiII you if you don't.
那就一起死.
Then everybody dies.
不, 我们交换.
No, we'II trade.
交换?
Trade?
我来换尔尼·奈尔斯
和莱森探员.
Ernie NiIes
and agent Bryson for me.
库.
Coop.
- 我要支援.
- 州警吗?
- I want backup.
- State poIice?
快叫他们来.
CaII them in.
露西, 我是豪克.
Lucy, it's Hawk.
给我接
州警.
Patch me through
to the state poIice.
我们的小男孩怎样了?
How's our baby boy?
熟睡了.
Sound asIeep.
做着爱之梦.
Dreaming of Iove.
幸运, 幸运, 真是个幸运仔.
Lucky, Iucky, Iucky boy.
幸运, 幸运, 幸运了.
Lucky, Iucky, Iucky.
他们把他挪到中间那个房里去了.
They moved him to the center room.
安迪, 稳住了.
Andy, keep steady.
更多警察来了.
More deputies.
还有阻击手.
Sharpshooters.
我们谈判还是跑路.
Let's deaI or Iet's run.
他们会让我们跑路吗, 库珀探员?
WiII they Iet us run, Agent Cooper?
不会.
No.
那你觉得他们愿意谈判吗?
So you think they wiII deaI?
不.
No.
那你说我们该怎么做?
What do you suggest we do?
投降.
Surrender.
好.
Okay.
你疯了?
Are you crazy?
不.
No.
但首先, 我们必须决定是这样
默默认输了还是先杀了他.
But first, we must decide
to give up quietIy or to kiII him.
- 那我们俩都得死.
- 我知道.
- Then we both die.
- I know.
我死对你如此重要吗?
Is my death so important to you?
我2个弟弟死了.
My two brothers died.
我要你负全责.
I hoId you responsibIe.
为什么?
Why?
在你来到这儿之前,
Before you came here,
双峰镇是个单纯的地方.
Twin Peaks was a simpIe pIace.
我弟弟不过卖卖毒品
给那些少年和卡车司机.
My brothers deaI dope
to the teenagers and the truck drivers.
商人和旅客在独眼杰克
鱼贯而行.
One-Eyed Jack's weIcomed
the businessmen and the tourists.
宁静的人们过着宁静的生活.
Quiet peopIe Iived a quiet Iife.
然后, 一个美女死了,
Then, a pretty girI die,
你来了,
一切都改变了.
and you arrive,
and everything change.
我弟弟伯拿,
My brother Bernard,
被开枪打死在树林里.
shot and Ieft to die in the woods.
一个悲痛欲绝的父亲用枕头
把我另一个仅存的弟弟也闷死了.
A grieving father smother
my remaining brother with a piIIow.
绑架. 死亡.
Kidnapping. Death.
突然, 宁静的人们,
不再宁静了.
SuddenIy, the quiet peopIe,
they're quiet no more.
冷不防, 单纯的梦
就成了噩梦.
SuddenIy, the simpIe dream
become the nightmare.
所以如果你死了,
也许就是最后一个了.
So if you die,
maybe you wiII be the Iast to die.
要么
你带着你的噩梦死去.
Maybe you brought
the nightmare with you.
要么噩梦
And maybe the nightmare
随你而逝.
wiII die with you.
我可搞不懂你现在来
说这些什么鬼话.
I don't know what the heII
you're taIking about.
我只知道
我们现在麻烦大了.
But I do know
we've got a damn probIem here.
如果你打算搞定它,
我来.
And if you're not gonna soIve it,
I wiII.
- 尚.
- 什么?
- Jean.
- What?
过来看看这.
Take a Iook at this.
- 你有点餐吗?
- 没有.
- You order any food?
- No.
不, 不, 不, 让她过来.
No, no, no, Iet her come.
让她过来.
Let her come.
只是个女孩子.
It's just a girI.
- 你好.
- 晚餐时间到了.
- HeIIo.
- Suppertime.
我在哪儿见过你不是?
Don't I know you?
你还好吧?
Are you okay?
还好.
Yeah.
好主意, 迪尼斯.
Quick thinking, Denise.
我不过借出1双美腿而已.
It was just my Iegs.
谢谢杜鲁门警长吧.
是他出的点子.
Thank Sheriff Truman.
It was his idea.
哈里·斯·杜鲁门.
Harry S. Truman.
有时候你就是得即兴发挥一下.
Sometimes you gotta improvise.
他死了.
He's dead.
波比?
Bobby?
波比, 别闹了.
Bobby, this isn't funny.
波比?
Bobby?
里欧?
Leo?
雪莉.
SheIIy.
- 炸弹. 你说什么, 炸弹?
- 从头讲起.
- Bomb. What do you mean, bomb?
- Start at the beginning.
那好, 有个人来电说
WeII, the voice on the phone said
有个炸弹埋在
树林里,
that there was a bomb
pIanted in the woods,
但没说是那个树林.
but it didn't say which woods.
然后突然间,
一个巨大的爆炸
Then aII of a sudden,
there was this huge expIosion
所有灯都熄了.
and aII the Iights went out.
所以我打了电话
给消防局.
So then I caIIed
the fire department.
- 做的好, 露西.
- 失火了?
- Good work, Lucy.
- Was there a fire?
有2处. 一个先是
在电力局.
Two of them. First there was one
at the power station.
但大部分的
义务消防员都--
But most
of the voIunteer fire department--
我去查看发动机.
有点不太对劲.
I'm gonna go check on the generator.
Something's not right.
好. 后来呢?
Okay. So?
--他们都在玩宾果游戏, 所以费了
好一阵子才集合起来.
--were pIaying bingo, so it took a whiIe
to get everybody together.
- 失陪了, 露西.
- 然后就是爆炸
- Excuse me, Lucy.
- Then there was the expIosion
我刚跟你说了, 听起来
好像就在楼上,
I toId you about, which sounded
Iike it was right upstairs,
所以我们都跑出去了.
嗯, 原来是变压器爆了
so we aII got out of here.
WeII, it turned out to be a transformer
就在楼的后面
一根电杆那.
on the poIe right behind
and above the buiIding.
那, 我们只好
等修好再进去
WeII, we had to wait
to go back inside
因为火化喷溅
到处都是
because it was shooting sparks
everywhere
我们好怕警局
也失火.
and we were afraid that the station
was gonna catch on fire too.
- 不过它没事.
- 他们找到原因了?
- But it didn't.
- Do they know how it started?
吉普长官说,
性质可疑.
Suspicious in nature,
that's what Chief KippIe said.
他当时吸入了浓烟
正难受着呢,
He was suffering
from smoke inhaIation at the time,
所以他嗓音有点点沙哑.
so he sounded a IittIe hoarse.
你应该听到他咳嗽的.
You shouId hear his cough.
我打算煮点鸡汤
给他补补.
I'm gonna make him
some chicken soup.
- 哈里?
- 怎么, 库.
- Harry?
- Yeah, Coop.
你最好自己
过来看看这个.
You'd better take a Iook
at this, aIone.
露西, 留在这儿.
Lucy, wait here.
老天爷！
Good Lord.
这是谁?
Who is it?
我不知道.
I don't know.
是一盘棋.
It's a chess game.
云顿·厄尔的下一个动作.
Windom EarIe's next move.